(Penny:)Oh, fine. You know, it's, been a while.
I'm getting back out there.
(Mrs Cooper:)Let me ask you, when you get back
out there, are you wearing this?
That top has paid for itseIf in free drinks,
Iike, 10 times what it cost.
Yes, Penny has a lot of money
tied up in promiscuity futures.
(Mrs Cooper:)Hon, you think maybe the reason
why you're having trouble...
...finding a guy is because you're letting
them ride the roller coaster...
(Mrs Cooper:)...without buying a ticket?
(Penny:)Oh, they don't always get to ride
the roller coaster.
(Penny:)Sometimes they only get to spin
the teacups.
I'm going out. Would it be crazy to ask
you to look at the outfit I'm gonna wear?
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, not crazy at all.
And don't beat yourseIf up.
(Mrs Cooper:)When I was your age,
you could have me for a car ride...
(Mrs Cooper:)- ...and a bottle of strawberry wine.
- Ha, ha.
Yeah, that will not be
in this week's e-mail blast.